put on oven gloves
take out oven tray
slice open pizza pack
put pizza on tray
slice off top of oven
slice off bottom onion
cut into onion to remove skin
pick up half of onion
slice half of onion, this onion
pick up half onion
slice half of onion
remove excess onion
walk to sink
turn on tap
rinse sponge
wash slicer
shake slicer
put slicer on drying rack
wash hand guard
rinse handguard
scrub hand guard
rinse hand guard
dry hand guard
open fridge
pick up olives
open olives
constrict (?) olives from jar
put on olive lids
open fridge
put away olives
pick up fork
throw in sink
rinse hands
pick up pepper
grab
pick up herbs
scrub chopping block
turn on tap
rinse fork
chopping block on drying rack
shake
[END SUBTITLE]